Because of my dad's job, my mom and sisters moved overseas,
so starting this spring, I started living alone.
However, my first time living alone lasted only a few days.
Hey, Rikka. I'm opening the door.
Wake up, already. We start school today.
Though I attempted to keep my dark chuunibyou history hidden,
and start life over again in high school,
just like I did last year,
Takanashi Rikka here foiled me again.
I command you to awaken, Takanashi!
Oh, Tyrant's Eye! The time of awakening has come!
Rikka, is sunny side up okay?
"Dark side up," please.
"Sunny side up" it is.
Turn over!
Which one?
I gave her too many options.
Yuuta!
What is it?
I don't have the ribbon for my uniform.
Huh?
No way! Was it them?!
I let my guard down.
That's why I told you to prepare it yesterday.
I'm opening the door.
This is a busy time! What do you think you're doing?!
I'll yank out your stupid cowlick!
Stop it! It's my "charm point"!
This spring, Rikka's mother also had to move out of town for work...
...which meant Rikka had to live on her own too, but...
Heave-ho, heave-ho, heave-ho...
Why is Rikka's baggage being moved out?!
Have they finally made their move?!
Eh? Her grandfather accidentally terminated the contract on their apartment?
This is sabotage!
I guess you'll have to move in with me until you've settled on a new place.
Emergency Code: Triple Four activating!
And so, Rikka came to live with me for a while.
It's nice to be woken up by you, Yuuta.
See it from my point of view.
The Priestess wouldn't be okay with that.
I lied to Touka-san and told her I found Rikka an apartment for her alone,
and we've been keeping up this facade for about a week.
Chimera, I give you my demonic fruit.
You're getting used to these red fruits.
This proves nothing!
Just give it a little try. They're as good as strawberries.
How can that be?!
You're becoming more and more like the Priestess.
Are you under her influence?!
It's for your own good.
Ah! Yuuta!
The fluid! The green gooey stuff is attacking me!
Wait, wait! Stay there.
Wiping it will just make it worse.
You need to dab it like this.
If you're heading out, please bring a collapsible umbrella with you.
You could say we're going out.
We're going out, but...
How do you even have romance if it has to be hidden?
I've never even had a normal girlfriend before...
so a chuunibyou girlfriend will be more difficult.
Things worked out not to be too different than before.
Guten morgen!
I'm Nibutani Shinka, and I'm starting my second year today.
Nibutani-san?
Nibutani-san!
How do you do, everyone?
Let's make it another good year.
Sure.
What's wrong with her?
High school second-year syndrome?
I'm going to say this one more time.
You'd better remember what we talked about yesterday.
Of course.
Based on the hieroglyphs, the magic barrier attack
triggered by the Freemasons...
Wrong!
Then maybe our uninvited guests from the inscrutable parallel world?
That's wrong too.
Do you mean performing Schrödinger's cat experiment using Chimera?
Never! We won't do that!
You know. About how we're living together at my place.
I see now, that's the one.
Isn't that the only thing we talked about?
We should visit the real estate agent again today.
If you are referring to my new base, it has already been located.
You serious?!
It is the demon world of the impossibly Wicked One,
invisible to mere mortals!
I thought you were being serious!
I'll yank out your stupid cowlick!
No, stop it!
Yo! Flirting this early in the morning?
Who are you?
It's me, Isshiki. Isshiki Makoto!
You know him?
Nope.
It's me! The guy in the Light Music Club!
The guy who sacrificed everything for Kumi-senpai!
Oh, it's the crew cut guy.
Mister Crew Cut!
Don't call me Crew Cut! That version of me is no longer!
Just look at my Rock'n'Roll hairdo!
Isshiki, what happened to your hair?
Huh?
Let's go visit the student councilor.
You've got it all wrong, Sensei.
My hair type changed when it grew back.
Yeah, yeah...
Hey, Kumin-senpai! Good morning!
I wonder who that was?
Kumin.
Rikka-chan! Togashi-kun! Morning.
You're both second-years starting today, right?
And now you're a third-year.
Uh-huh. And it's  so much responsibility.
Ah, because of studying for university.
Uh-uh, that isn't what I mean. I'm disappointed.
Want to know why?
Why?
Because high school third year is a "turd" year!
That's strange...
That's how it told me to deliver it.
Um, what is that?
You know? I want to make everyone laugh just like how Morisummer-chan did.
Growing older brings many changes.
Morisummer-chan!
Morning! What's up with your outfit...
How do you do, Kumin-senpai.
I am wearing normal attire.
"How do you do?"
Do you maybe have early-onset dementia?
Senpai, if I might have a word...
Morisummer-chan, where are we going?
Death.
So then, let's make this another spirited school year!
Thank you for that.
I'll show you.
I made a lot of mistakes...
but my second year will be completely different.
I swear I will claw my way to the top of this school!
The next speech comes from our new students...
represented by Dekomori Sanae-san.
Wha-?!
I am the new student representative, Dekomori Sanae.
With the warm days of Spring...
the trees become enrobed in fresh, new green livery.
They say that she got better grades than you had last year, Nibutani-san.
Our student lives also begin anew.
Mm?
That's just great.
Deko!
Hey, what happened?
Ahem.
I believe everyone knows that there are both white and black worlds.
Wha-?
"Seeing spirits requires the proper heart."
"Love is everything."
Hey, are you all right?
Sensei, Nibutani-san has fainted!
What are they doing, those guys?
We're in the same class again, Light Being.
What are you saying, Takanashi-san?
Are you okay?
Takanashi-san!
We're in the same class!
Let's have another good year.
Let's.
Nanase-sensei is our home room teacher.
Togashi.
Wah!
They told me to get my hair cut by tomorrow.
What do I do?
Like I'd know? This is your fault!
Wait, are we in the same class again?
No, I'm in Class 3 next door.
Really?
Is that relief?!
You didn't even try to hide your relief at all !
Togashi-kun, a moment.
Who is this babe?
Pleased to meet you.
Are you Togashi's friend? I'm Nibutani—
Pot, meet kettle.
I'm only bringing this up because we're in the same class.
I told Tatenashi-san not to mention our middle school matters at all, period.
You're still going on about that?
I considered it all summer break.
About whether I'd be going to this high school.
Do I really intend to spend three years of my life in that loser's club—
Hey, are you okay?
Servant to the Tyrant's Eye!
The Mjolnir Hammer, Dekomori Sanae...
...is hereby reborn!
Only the deviously devious Fake Morisummer
would dare attack Dekomori in her temporary guise.
Your very nature disgusts me!
Now watch carefully!
I spin right-to-left, and left-to-right.
The opposing revolutions shall produce a kink between dimensions and space!
And by adding an additional revolution, I shall produce unlimited power!
Take this! The Mjolnir...
You sure have weak semicircular canals.
Dekomori will not be defeated!
Because you're such an energetic first-year...
as a reward, I will give you the cheese you love. So. Much.
Don't you think you're overdoing it?
One must take responsibility for one's creations.
Paging a student.
Takanashi-san from Year 2, Class 4. Takanashi Rikka-san.
Please report to the staff room immediately. I repeat.
Takanashi-san from Year 2, Class 4,
please report to the staff room immediately.
The school has been overrun by terrorists!
No it hasn't.
Letters?
Mm. The school mailed at least three to your home, you know.
They were all returned to sender.
Perhaps because my existence had been erased from this world.
When we phone you, it says that number is not in use.
My existence had been erased.
But you exist right now, so perhaps it'll go through now.
It won't.
Why not?
My eye! My eye!
That's not going to work!
She seemed to buy it, but at this rate, it'll get ugly.
That's not true!
Really now?
Can't you just try to take a bite?
Rikka, would you like to come sit with us here?
No, I'm good.
The incubus lives in that coffin.
Even I, who was forged in darkness, dare not approach.
I once experienced a frightening dream while under its influence.
Really? What was the dream about?
Ugh, the light! The Light Being is paralyzing me!
What're you doing?
Ow?
Why did that sound questioning?
No particular reason.
In what place would you choose to reside?
Reside?
What we were talking just a moment ago.
Regarding your base and battle formation!
For the base, which the Tyrant's Eye and the Dark Flame Master demand,
will be the base where the magical magnetic field is also the strongest.
You know that won't happen.
I know...
Nibutani.
Oh, what's with that outfit?
Is that idiot here?
Look what she did to my costume for Theatre Club!
She's sleeping inside.
Sleeping?
Then that's convenient...
Later!
Later.
What, you're leaving?
Ah, kinda.
We are going to search for a new base.
Enough already, let's go!
Base?
After all that...
I have no idea where you should find your own
I desire a underground labyrinth. But an ancient castle is also okay.
Is there such a thing?
Opposite the convenience store, there's a castle with "British Parliament" on it.
Idiot! You definitely can't do that!
Ah, Yuuta.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize how expensive rent is...
I mean, I knew it might be expensive.
Actually, I don't know much about it either.
It has to be expensive.
Yuuta.
If I transfer to a new base, will I not be able to come here?
There's no reason for that.
But when I go to and from school, I won't come here.
Yeah, it'll probably be like that.
I won't be able to go to your room to report activity in the magical realm.
It would be good if you don't come.
But...
I'll drop by to pick you up for school.
Let's search for a place that we can play at and is nearby.
Don't you want to stay together?
You two!
Nibutani.
Takanashi-san's apartment is empty. What's going on?
Did you move, Rikka-chan?
Well, about that...
Could I have an explanation?
Touka...-san?!
We're leaving for Italy soon, but you won't give me your new home's address. Nor answer your phone.
What's going on?
Uh, that's not it, um...
Yuuta! Run!
Idiot!
I see. You remain unwilling to say anything.
Master!
Dekomori!
I was right to chase Fake Summer!
Your servant Dekomori will buy you time!
Masters, please evacuate to safety!
Do you realize who you're up against?
Of course!
She is the priestess who, in a previous battle once force-fed Dekomori a mass of rotten dairy!
There is no worthier opponent.
Now, come at me!
Hey, you! Your hand! Your hand!
Now I know what you guys intend to do.
No! You're wrong! This is...this is Fake Morisummer's doing!
What are you saying?! This was your fault to begin with!
Dekomori deeply respects you, Priestess!
As my master's sister, I am at your command!
Stop trying to throw me under the bus!
You two are such good friends...
Oh, sorry. My hand slipped.
Ehh?
All hands, prepare for combat!
Assume positions and prepare to intercept!
Be destroyed, real.
Burst open, synapses!
Vanishment this world!
Dark Matter Blaze.
It's still no good!
She easily deflected master's Dark Matter Blaze.
What kind of person is she?
It's all or nothing!
L!
LO!
LOV!
LOVE!
How about a physical attack?
Direct Impact!
Machine Gun!
Yuuta!
Schwarz Shield!
Arrostire!
What's arrostire?
It means "oven roasted."
Yuuta!
Hot!
You're living together?!
Really?!
Like I said, it's not what you think.
In what way?
You're living together as boyfriend and girlfriend.
Please control your disgusting imagination.
What do you mean, disgusting?
I think you're the one with the dirty mind.
W-what? I, Dekomori, am always pure of thought!
You're totally red!
For a little kid, you have a really dirty mind.
Be quiet! Be quiet, you big-boobed freak!
Hey, stop that!
Shacking is sooo shocking!
That hurt!
Anyway, it's really not what you think...
...and we had no choice.
You're saying that a high school boy
and my little sister, who are in a romantic relationship
had no choice but to move in together?
No th-that's not what I meant!
You are not in a romantic relationship?
Uh, no...
You guys broke up?
You dissolved your pact?
Who dumped whom?
Quit it! I'm saying we didn't "move in together"!
How is that different?
Yes, we are living together...
because I was worried about leaving Rikka on her own.
It's been almost a week now, and nothing of that sort is going on.
Of what sort?
Stop it, all of you!
How about it?
Our contract remains unaltered.
In other words, we didn't "move in together"...
That's it! It's home share!
It's a home share situation. You know—
Ow!
Do you think that logic will work on me?
Do you think I will permit that?
You are a boy!
My magazine!
In any case, you can't live together.
I will find her an apartment. If you have a problem with that...
...I will take Rikka to Italy with me.
Italy?
The magical society! The Cardinal!
Am I to be imprisoned in such a place?
Italy is home to the occult!
The Vatican, Sixth Sense, I see dead people!
Home to the occult?
So, you want to go now?
Yes?
I'm home.
Good evening.
Kuzuha, why are you here?
I came home.
Didn't you hear I was coming back for the new school term?
Heard? From whom?
From Mom.
Oops, I forgot!
You've been living together with Rikka?
That should be okay, right?
Huh?
That is, she doesn't have a home, right?
We have plenty of rooms here.
You're sure it's okay?
To be honest, I felt uneasy about Rikka living alone.
If you little sister supervises, it should be okay.
I'm sorry. Please let her stay here just a little longer.
Sure.
Understood. You can count on me.
Hurry up and find your own place!
And so, my life alone with Rikka came to an abrupt end...
and three teenagers began life together in spring.
Yuuta's notebook. I forgot to return it to him.
Rikka?
That girl...!
What the-?
Did someone new move in?
She never was able to get her apartment back.
To be continued