Togashi's place?
Yup! After all, they've shacked up!
Shacked up!
Don't you want to have a peek?
Shacking up isn't all that shocking.
Enough!
My master merely shares a hideout
with Dark Flame Master
under the terms of their formal contract.
They are not living the
scandalous life you imagine.
She's right.
And besides, Togashi asked us
not to talk about it at school.
I know that.
But they're in high school!
They're boyfriend and girlfriend!
And they're living together!
Doesn't it bother you?
The only thing that bothers me
is a decrepit non-sorcerer like yourself.
I am busy. Now be quiet.
What are you doing, Deko?
I am creating an adventure log for my fallen
comrades who have retreated
from the front line.
Adventure log?
She's assembling lesson notes
for classmates who weren't at school.
All right, you stay behind.
Are you interested, Kumin?
Hmm...
A couple in love, living together.
I bet their hearts flutter when they
make eye contact.
I bet they have little cuddles
when nobody's around.
I'll bet they even sneak kisses
when Little Sister isn't looking.
What? Really?
LOVE LOVE
Well, yeah!
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
Be quiet!
Be quiet! Be quiet! Be quiet!
So, it does bother you.
It does not!
The dark wave motions prevent me
from seeing my master.
I cannot see her.
Master... Where are you, Master?
Face it. It seriously bothers you.
You finished off those lesson notes
incredibly fast.
Oh! I see Togashi!
You're right! What is he doing?
He's either testing the wind direction...
...or he is ordering the dark ones
to assemble for a new battle.
I think...
...he's taking in the laundry.
I'm sorry. I forgot to take it in.
No, I believe it was Rikka's turn today.
That's all right. I've
always done the laundry.
Dolphin Ring Striker
That won't work. She's
the one who suggested it.
BADDY
Yes. The Wicked Lord's chaotic trance
dark hot pot is served.
You're calling it dark hot pot.
Rikka, my big brother and I will take care
of all the cooking from now on.
Understood.
Please assign me a different mission.
We only started assigning chores
because of her messes.
Is she here?
She just got in.
You were supposed to die then!
Use the vacuum.
What are you doing in here anyway?
Ooh! Did you buy those?
I-I did not "buy" anything.
It was preordained that these
should fall into my hands.
Those are so cool! Let me see!
Sure.
Here.
Thanks!
You could use these to
play ghost busters too!
Ooh, you look so cool!
Yuta!
Do your own vacuuming.
But these must have been expensive.
I'm surprised you had the money.
EVERY WHICH WAY BANK
RIKKA TAKANASHI
Toka mentioned that she'd deposited
your monthly allowance.
Rikka. No, Wicked Lord Shingan.
Will you please show me your
gold documentation?
This is my Wicked Lord Shingan's
most secret secret.
I cannot disclose that secret, even to you!
Show it to me, Wicked Lord Shingan.
If you open it, all the evil
contained therein will escape
and spread over the Earth...
Just show it to me!
Yuta, stop!
What is the meaning of this?
Power Level: 150,000?
He is more powerful than the Priestess!
Apologize to your sister!
You! You!
Wah, stop!
That's how they act at school.
We can't be sure just yet.
After all, couples don't
act lovey-dovey all the time.
Hey, someone's moved
into the apartment above.
PAKIRA
FRESH MARKET
Were you really planning to ride out
the rest of the month on less than 1000 yen?
One of Wicked Lord Shingan's abilities
is the empty rupture.
The magic of Wicked Lord Shingan
who dwells within me...
...can maintain my bodily functions
without nourishment for years...
...enabling life activity.
NEW PRODUCT!!!
Arabiki Crunchy Sausages
Would you like a sample?
See? You are hungry.
I'm sorry, I'll take two bags.
Going out to shop together for food
for supper is much more romantic.
We're going in.
You're dragging me down.
A sign said 'no roller skates in the store.'
My foe could attack at any time,
but I'm ready for them.
I will topple that pile of
candy and block them off.
And then I will immediately
destroy the lighting.
And when they have been blinded,
I'll finish them with this.
Offense and defense as one!
Don't do it, ever!
Look how late it is. Let's go.
Wait.
CUMIN
Kumin!
Yuta, we must purchase Kumin.
We don't need any. Put it back.
What? C'mon, we need to buy Kumin!
Rikka is so cute.
What about Dekomori?
Maybe they have Dekomori!
You're not a spice, dummy.
These are cumin seeds.
Effective for putting monsters to sleep.
Cumin is used for making curry.
We don't make authentic curry at our house.
The usual roux cubes will suffice.
Do you have something against Kumin?
I never said that. C'mon, we're going.
She seems to have split up with Togashi.
What is she staring at?
Today, I will have the blue crystal.
MYSTERY JEWEL
Are you done? Let's go.
Yuta, I must go to verify the
condition of a singularity.
At your leave.
What, now?
Make it back home by supper time.
I swear it on the name of
the Wicked Lord Shingan.
My Master summons me!
I'm on my way! Dekomori is on her way!
It's so nice that they're such good friends.
Although they didn't look that lovey-dovey.
That's the problem.
Huh?
They've been going out for six months.
This is the time most couples are
supposed to be at their busiest.
Really?
But look at the state of them. I suspect...
...marital burnout!
Burnout paradise!
That hurt, Morisummer.
You're supposed to respect your senpai.
But really, you're burning out.
So you say.
How do you feel about Takanashi?
In what way?
You're boyfriend and girlfriend, aren't you?
You've sounded out your feelings
for one another, haven't you?
Well, yeah, sure.
Don't you feel excitement
when you're together?
Don't you hold hands and
gaze into one another's eyes?
T-that has nothing to do with you.
Just tell me.
She hasn't changed a bit in the last year.
And you seem totally oblivious too.
Oblivious?!
I spied on you two yesterday...
...and you looked more like father
and daughter than a couple.
More like grampa and grandkid.
Who are you calling grampa?
You were tailing us?!
So, you don't like cumin, huh?
What are you talking about?!
You've shacked up! Togashi,
you're living with your girlfriend!
Don't you ever bill and
coo like normal couples?
I think you're wrong about
the marital burnout thing.
Why?
Because that refers to a couple growing
dispassionate about one another.
In our case, me and Rikka,
we haven't even gotten to
the hand-holding stage.
Wha-?
Really!
Yeah. So, the marital burnout thing...
...really doesn't apply to us.
Yuta Togashi.
Why does that make you so angry anyway?!
When did you start going out?
Last fall.
When did you go on a boat date?
Christmas.
So, you're saying that New Year's Eve
and Valentine's Day went by...
...and you still haven't
even held hands yet?!
You're choking me, Nibutani.
Come with me!
Wait! Wait, Nibutani!
Togashi, look what they did to me.
Move it!
This is Kazari Kannagi!
Hello, my name is Kazari.
Oh.
Kannagi knows everything to do with romance.
I'm sure she'll give you good advice.
Wait, what are you talking about?
I told you to keep me and Rikka
living together a secret.
I know that. I didn't tell her that.
I only told her that your love life
isn't going so well.
Rikka is your girlfriend, right?
Huh? Uh, well, it's kind of...
Why hide it?
You two have been famous
ever since Year One.
I see, so you're having problems with Rikka.
This could be my big chance.
Pardon?
I actually like girls.
And I'm infatuated with Rikka.
I didn't tell her because if she found out,
that would be the end of it.
You're my rival? I hope
that is the end of it!
But all joking aside...
That was a joke?
For now, please give me your cell phone.
Sure.
The best thing to do is ask her on a date,
set the right mood, and see how she reacts.
Wait, what are you doing with my phone?!
I'm sending mail. "Will you please go out
on a date with me this Sunday?"
What?!
"I have something important to talk
to you about." Send.
Hey!
That was kind of exciting because
it was like telling Rikka I love her.
Look here!
We may look calm...
...but every girl waits for the boy
to make the first move.
Even Rikka?
I could be wrong.
Takanashi can't say what's on her mind,
partly due to her syndrome.
You need to coax her out of her shell.
Well, yeah, you could have a point.
Sender: Rikka Takanashi
ROGER THAT.
And so, Rikka and I,
albeit unintentionally...
...made a date for Sunday.
Good morning, Water Dragon.
Good morning.
Rikka, that's so cute.
The use of this robe is only permitted
for special ceremonies.
Really? Is something special happening today?
Okay, let's go.
Tell me first. What is our destination?
Well, it's a place you
kind of wanted to visit.
I did?
Gasp! Are you reading my thoughts?!
No! Just wait and see.
Got a firm grip?
Releasing evil skill formula.
Deployment prep complete.
Yuta, we have a green light. Go!
But slowly.
Yes, ma'am.
How is it? You okay?
No problem, other than poor visibility.
There's nothing we can
do about your visibility.
I need to concentrate on safe driving.
Don't worry. Your death is also my death.
You're scaring me.
And besides, the Wicked Lord
Shingan is all-powerful!
He allows me to see everything,
despite my visibility.
I can even see into your soul.
That's the first time you
mentioned that ability.
Right now, you are thinking,
"Whoa! I'm breaking the sound barrier!"
"I am a virtual whirlwind of
lightning speed!" Right?
I am not!
Oh! Look!
Wind turbines.
Ha!
What are you doing?
I will rotate the windmills using dark power!
Join me, Yuta!
That won't work.
Don't worry. We just need to unite
our dark powers as one!
Will this do?
Wicked Lord Fire Dragon wave motion!
C'mon, let's go.
I saw an internet video showing a windmill
being destroyed by gale-force winds.
SAZANAMI AQUARIUM
Ooh. It's the reincarnation of R'lyeh.
Remember how you said
you wanted to see a real dolphin?
Mister Kyle is a genius.
He is in the form of a fish...
...but I suspect he is actually
a dark warrior in disguise.
I haven't seen him around recently.
My dear Ancient Kings.
We may look calm...
...but every girl waits for the boy
to make the first move.
Rikka...
Listen. Since we're here,
just the two of us...
...would you like to hold hands?
Uh, you don't have to if you're too shy.
It's just that we've only touched pinkies...
...since we started going out.
Wow, penguins! Penguins!
Nautilus!
No, no. "Nau-t-lus."
I once seriously wanted to attend
Miskatonic University...
...but the Mu civilization was never
an existing continent.
And Mister Kyle only existed
in the Japanese version.
What? For real?
Such incredible speed.
The speed to tear through magical dimensions.
Now, if you would like to give signals to
the dolphin, show me your flippers!
Me! Me!
All right, that girl there.
Coming!
Will you please tell us
your name and your age?
I... I'm Rikka Takanashi. I'm...
I'm in grade six.
Don't tell her that!
Look hard at the dolphin's face,
and sway your head from side to side.
Calm down, Dolphin!
Are you okay? Shall I dry your face?
I'm fine!
Okay, next let's get the
training lady teach you...
...how to give the signal to jump.
First, point upward with your right hand.
Next, touch your right hand
to your left shoulder.
To give the signal, we will count to three...
...and then you must raise your right hand.
Let's begin. One, two, three!
The dolphin is at my bidding!
Cut it out, silly!
Come on, diving beetle!
Oh! A Japanese giant salamander!
That wasn't much different
from the norm either.
You need to coax her out of her shell.
I'm sure she's right, but...
I'm here.
Shakey shake!
I'll let you have this with it.
This returns from vending machines
every single time.
The Chosen 10 yen coin!
Hey, I don't get excited
about every little thing!
Uh-oh. Did I miss?
But it isn't a serrated
10 yen coin after all.
It's so old, the edge got smoothed down.
Poor thing. You have lost
your place in the world.
It has merely lost its place in the
vending machine system.
It's still good currency.
But then it would lose its
predominance as the Chosen One.
Make up your mind.
Today was fun, huh?
A dolphin tore through the darkness!
And we even held hands.
Y-yeah. I'll hold hands.
All you can hold, hand-holding!
Sure.
But I still don't understand it that well.
I made the love pact with you,
so we are boyfriend and girlfriend.
But I still don't have the
slightest idea what lovers are.
Thinking about it makes my head confused.
Rikka.
Now that we are lovers,
regular physical contact is inevitable!
Th-that's true.
However...
Which is it?
I don't know.
I searched for the meaning of lovers...
...but it's still unclear to me.
I searched the net, but it was gibberish.
What does "Common-law couples are not
necessarily designated as lovers" even mean?!
It's totally different from my contract
with Wicked Lord Shingan.
Do you mean you didn't want the love pact?
I didn't say that! I do want it!
I'm happy about it!
But I don't know what I should be doing.
Although I'm certain
that something must change.
I can say one thing with certainty.
A fun day is coming to an end.
We will soon go home.
Together to the same place.
Nothing could make me happier.
So happy in fact, that I fear I've peaked,
and am now marked for death.
Hey,
it's turning!
Our powers worked on it.
The Wicked Lord Shingan
is definitely invincible!
Oh! But The Dark Flame Master
is second-most invincible.
Yuta?
Sorry, it isn't that.
I am impressed, Wicked Lord Shingan!
You are indeed the one, I,
Dark Flame Master, expected you to be!
The contract you and I are bound to
is not the so-called lover's
pact of the mundanes!
It is the lover's pact of
the Wicked Lord Shingan!
Therefore, we need not feel
the obligation to be manipulated
by the so-called conventional
wisdom of commoners!
We may fulfill our contract as we see fit!
I am certain we can fulfill this pact!
For we are the Wicked Lord Shingan
and Dark Flame Master!
Yuta.
So, what do you think?
Sure.
You turned the windmills and came home?
That doesn't make any sense.
And you're really okay with that?
Yeah.
I think that Rikka still needs to be Rikka.
I feel a lot better now.
Well, if you're okay with it.
But Kannagi gave me some advice.
She said that if a couple keeps
putting everything off...
...it nearly always gives an interloper
the chance to come between them.
Oof, oof.
Wanna see my magic?
To be Continued