mebuita yamiyo ga haran he to hakobu
Out from a dark night, troubles are brewing
waku waku suru ne
Isn't that exciting?
nanatsu no oto enyou yori hanatarete
The seven sounds came forth from the deep sea
doki doki suru ne
Doesn't that make your heart race?
matsui no rakuin anshou ni hirameku
The Matsui brand shines from the sunken reef
mada tsudzukeru ki nano
You're still going on about that?
ai no setsuri ni kakka matataku
The providence of love flickers hotly
mou yamenasai
Stop it already!
bokura wa hitotsu ni nari ten mo kakete
We will become one and soar through the sky
hokori wa sakebi chiru
Our pride screams and scatters
hanabi no you da
Like fireworks
kagayaki wa setsuna ni hazeta
In a moment, the radiance bursts open
douke wa seigi no tategami mo hashirasete
The buffoon runs from the mane of justice
gusha wa tsukikage ni kyomou idaku
The fool embraces delusions of moonlight
geimu ga bokura wo oitsumeru tame ni aru naraba
If the purpose of this game is to drive us into a corner
semete kuchinu hodo no baka de aritai
At least let my foolishness go on
break through tamashi de hoeta
"Break through!" my soul roared
Van!shiment Th!s World!
Vanishment this world!