Moving Company
Danger
Person Name
Item Name
Fragile Item
Yes・No
・No
Fragile Item
Item Name
Person Name
The Revival of...The Wicked Eye
Art of Comedic Conversation
Making people laugh!
DEKOMORI
High
Going out later is
a detour!
Wash hands!
Going out later is
a detour!
Wash hands!
Rich Cheese (6 pcs)
Far-East Magical Napping Society
Summer Version
FAKE
Emergency Exit
PERMANENT MARKER
House for Rent
Deposit
Gratitude Money
Station Nearby!!
5 minute walk from station
Sunlight
Air
Real Estate Agent Kabu
Real Estate Agent
Apartments, Units
Room Searching
No Bicycle Parking
DUMMY
MA
SHIN
GAN(DEMON GOD GUN)
Top Left: monthly Top right: April issue Right: Attention Idol Group Below far right: debut appearance
First magazine: top: monthly  Upper middle right: Special issue Middle right: Special girls poster and DVD attached   Middle left :to dominate interview  Bottom Left: dual sided pages
2nd magazine: Top right: debut appearance on top to dominate interview    Bottom right: 50 idol trading cards included  Very bottom right: dual sided pages
TOGASHI MAIL FOR NAKANISHI HERE